You can only choose one.
Eternity is a romance, comedy, drama film directed by David Freyne.
In an afterlife where souls have one week to decide where to spend eternity, Joan is faced with the impossible choice between
the man she spent her life with and her first love, who died young and has waited decades for her to arrive.
Joan, played by Elizabeth Olsen.
Larry, played by Miles Teller.
Luke, played by Callum Turner.
Anna, played by Da'Vine Joy Randolph.
Ryan, played by John Early.
Older Larry, played by Barry Primus.
Eternity is a 2025 American fantasy romantic comedy film directed by
David Freyne, who co-wrote the film with Pat Cunnane.
The film stars Elizabeth Olsen, Miles Teller, and Callum Turner.
Its plot follows a woman who must choose between two men
with whom to spend eternity in the afterlife.
Da'Vine Joy Randolph, John Early, and Olga Merediz appear in supporting roles.
Eternity premiered at the Toronto International Film Festival on September 7, 2025, and
was theatrically released in the United States by A24 on November 26, 2025.
The film received positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of afterlife, romcom,
first love, eternity, introspective.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.